Zein
أيّ
you're the only one who can save Supremo
أنت الوحيد القادر على إنقاذ سوبريمو
and this university.
وهذه الجامعة.
We can do this.
بإمكاننا فعل ذلك.
Don't give up.
لا تستسلم.
I hope after this night ends
أتمنى بعد انتهاء هذه الليلة
you can still forgive me.
لا يزال بإمكانك أن تسامحني.
Do you want me to repeat myself?
هل تريدني أن أكرر كلامي؟
I can't take this pain anymore, Ace.
لم أعد أحتمل هذا الألم يا إيس.
Did you ever love Ace Craige?
هل أحببتَ يومًا ما آيس كريج؟
No.
لا.
Did you really love me?
هل كنت تحبني حقاً؟
Who could endure loving you?
من يستطيع تحمل حبك؟
I want you to fight.
أريدك أن تقاتل.
Not for me
ليس لي
but for your friends.
لكن من أجل أصدقائك.
Most especially for yourself.
وخاصة لنفسك.
No matter what happens
بغض النظر عما يحدث
you'll always be
ستبقى دائماً
my queen.
ملكتي.
Liam Rivera is.
ليام ريفيرا هو.
Madam Violet's son?
ابن السيدة فيوليت؟
She wants Liam to be the Supremo.
إنها تريد أن يكون ليام هو الزعيم الأعلى.
Don't you recognize this symbol?
ألا تتعرف على هذا الرمز؟
This is the symbol of Raze Silvenia.
هذا هو رمز ريز سيلفينيا.
I want you to fight.
أريدك أن تقاتل.
Not for me
ليس لي
but for your friends
لكن من أجل أصدقائك
and especially yourself.
وخاصة نفسك.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm still breathing
ما زلت أتنفس
and a promise is a promise.
والوعد وعد.
Hoy...
اليوم...
Hoy.
اليوم.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Why did you turn your back on him?
لماذا أدرت ظهرك له؟
Why didn't you fight for him?
لماذا لم تقاتل من أجله؟
Darling?
محبوب؟
Don't call me that!
لا تناديني بهذا الاسم!
Let go.
اتركه.
I said let go!
قلتُ: دعني أذهب!
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Darling
محبوب
please come back.
أرجو العودة.
Supremo asked me to send this message.
طلب مني سوبريمو إرسال هذه الرسالة.
Supremo...
سوبريم...
Raze Silvenia
بداية سيلفينيا
who are you really?
من أنت حقاً؟
One!
واحد!
Two!
اثنين!
Three!
ثلاثة!
Are you an ally
هل أنت حليف؟
or an enemy?
أم عدو؟
Let his wound bleed.
دع جرحه ينزف.
Clean it with warm water until he's clean from the poison.
نظفه بالماء الدافئ حتى يزول السم.
Something got into Vanessa's eye.
دخل شيء ما في عين فانيسا.
I was just helping her get it out.
كنت أساعدها فقط في إخراجها.
Your breath stinks! Stop it!
رائحة فمك كريهة! توقف عن ذلك!
Whatever, guys.
مهما يكن يا رفاق.
As if it's not obvious.
وكأن الأمر ليس واضحاً.
So...
لذا...
where have you been?
أين كنت؟
It's almost Bloody Night!
اقتربت ليلة الدم!
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Wow
رائع
so that's how she is when she's in love.
هكذا هي حالتها عندما تكون واقعة في الحب.
She's so different now.
لقد تغيرت كثيراً الآن.
Right, Je?
صحيح، أليس كذلك؟
You're right, my Vanessa.
معك حق يا فانيسا.
Hey!
يا!
And when did I belong you?
ومتى أصبحتُ أنتمي إليك؟
Hmm...
همم...
Yesterday, when you kissed me.
بالأمس، عندما قبلتني.
Excuse me!
اعذرني!
I tripped! I didn't mean to do that!
تعثرت! لم أكن أقصد ذلك!
Oh my god.
يا إلهي.
Wow.
رائع.
She tripped
تعثرت
right on my lips.
مباشرة على شفتي.
Right?
يمين؟
Why did you turn your back on him?
لماذا أدرت ظهرك له؟
Why didn't you fight for him
لماذا لم تقاتل من أجله؟
darling?
محبوب؟
Don't call me that!
لا تناديني بهذا الاسم!
I'm sorry, Ace.
أنا آسف يا إيس.
I can't come back to you.
لا أستطيع العودة إليك.
Let's just let fate decide what happens.
دعونا نترك القدر يقرر ما سيحدث.
There's still a lot that can happen.
لا يزال هناك الكثير مما يمكن أن يحدث.
I refuse to be your weakness.
أرفض أن أكون نقطة ضعفك.
During wartime
خلال زمن الحرب
it was common for wives, fiancées, and girlfriends
كان من الشائع أن تقوم الزوجات والخطيبات والصديقات بـ
to be kept waiting for years on end.
أن يُجبروا على الانتظار لسنوات طويلة.
The lucky ones carried on correspondence through letters.
أما المحظوظون فقد استمروا في المراسلات عبر الرسائل.
Most of the women
معظم النساء
held onto those letters from their loved ones.
احتفظوا بتلك الرسائل من أحبائهم.
Just think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Some letters arrive late.
بعض الرسائل تصل متأخرة.
Some don't even make it on time to hold meaning.
بعضها لا يصل حتى في الوقت المناسب ليحمل معنى.
And sadly, some never arrive at all.
وللأسف، لا يصل البعض على الإطلاق.
For what?
لماذا؟
People continued to write.
استمر الناس في الكتابة.
- They wrote about ordinary - You know...
- لقد كتبوا عن العاديين - كما تعلمون...
things like what they ate that day.
أشياء مثل ما تناولوه في ذلك اليوم.
The most mundane things.
أكثر الأشياء عادية.
Because during war, ordinary life becomes something precious.
لأن الحياة العادية تصبح شيئاً ثميناً خلال الحرب .
Loving each other briefly was enough.
كان حب كل منهما للآخر لفترة وجيزة كافياً.
No, it's not.
لا، ليس كذلك.
I want to love you
أريد أن أحبك
openly.
علنًا.
Darling
محبوب
why can't you trust me?
لماذا لا تستطيع أن تثق بي؟
I trust you, Ace
أثق بك يا إيس.
with my whole life.
بكل حياتي.
I'm giving up.
سأستسلم.
I just can't fight for this shit anymore.
لم أعد أستطيع القتال من أجل هذا الهراء.
We haven't even started yet
لم نبدأ بعد
and you're ending it just like that?
وأنت تنهي الأمر بهذه البساطة؟
Darling...
محبوب...
Stop calling me that.
توقف عن مناداتي بذلك.
Zein
أيّ
I'll give you another chance.
سأمنحك فرصة أخرى.
If you walk ten steps away from me
إذا ابتعدت عني عشر خطوات
and you don't look back,
ولا تنظر إلى الوراء،
forget everything between us.
انسَ كل شيء بيننا.
Here
هنا
these are your new clothes.
هذه ملابسك الجديدة.
Wear it
ارتديه
and I'll show you our office.
وسأريك مكتبنا.
And where do you think you're going?
وإلى أين تظن نفسك ذاهباً؟
To the restroom
إلى دورة المياه
to change.
للتغيير.
No.
لا.
Change here.
غيّر هنا.
In front of you?
أمامك؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Do you want to?
هل تريد أن؟
In your dreams.
في أحلامك.
You still lack training.
ما زلت تفتقر إلى التدريب.
Just so you know
للعلم فقط
those aren't just the moves I know.
هذه ليست مجرد الحركات التي أعرفها.
Maybe you'd like to move your hand off me?
ربما ترغب في إبعاد يدك عني؟
I told you
أخبرتك
you can look at me
يمكنك أن تنظر إلي
but you're not allowed to touch me.
لكن لا يُسمح لك بلمسي.
I'm ready to fight even death for you.
أنا مستعد لمواجهة الموت من أجلك.
This tastes disgusting.
طعمه مقرف.
Don't spit it out!
لا تبصقها!
Supremo?
الأفضل؟
Whatever you choose
أياً كان اختيارك
as long as it makes you happy.
طالما أن ذلك يجعلك سعيداً.
Whatever your decision is
أياً كان قرارك
don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
I think
أظن
this is really goodbye for us.
هذا وداعٌ حقيقي لنا.
I love you.
أحبك.
Zein.
أيها؟
♪ Oh darling. ♪
♪ يا حبيبي. ♪
♪ How beautiful it is to love you. ♪
♪ ما أجمل أن أحبك. ♪
♪ I will lie beside you. ♪
♪ سأستلقي بجانبك. ♪
♪ I'll always be here for you. ♪
سأكون دائمًا هنا من أجلك.
♪ Darling... ♪
♪ حبيبي... ♪
You're wasting your energy by staring, Ms. Shion.
أنتِ تهدرين طاقتكِ بالتحديق يا آنسة شيون.
He's still not here?
ألم يأتِ بعد؟
I haven't seen him all day.
لم أره طوال اليوم.
Maybe he's not planning to come back.
ربما لا يخطط للعودة.
No way.
مستحيل.
Or maybe
أو ربما
he's with someone else?
هل هو مع شخص آخر؟
Kidding
يمازج
of course.
بالطبع.
Be patient, Ms. Shion.
تحلّي بالصبر يا آنسة شيون.
He'll return.
سيعود.
I just want this day to be over.
أريد فقط أن ينتهي هذا اليوم.
Same.
نفس.
All of us feel that way.
كلنا نشعر بذلك.
I know what's bothering you.
أعرف ما يزعجك.
Fuck off, Nicky.
انصرف يا نيكي.
I saw him.
رأيته.
He's with someone.
إنه برفقة شخص ما.
I didn't ask.
لم أسأل.
But that's not what your eyes are telling me.
لكن هذا ليس ما تخبرني به عيناك.
You’re so fragile
أنت هش للغاية
and easy to break, Zein.
وسهل الكسر يا زين.
Where’s that monster you’re hiding?
أين ذلك الوحش الذي تختبئ فيه؟
Let it go, Zein.
دع الأمر يمر يا زين.
Protect yourself.
احمِ نفسك.
Thanks for the advice.
شكراً على النصيحة.
Next.
التالي.
Hi, Supremo.
مرحباً، سوبريم.
Thanks for last night.
شكراً على الليلة الماضية.
I really appreciate it.
أنا ممتنٌ حقاً.
Anything for you, Supremo.
أي شيء لأجلك يا سوبريمو.
Is it true that dogs can't look up?
هل صحيح أن الكلاب لا تستطيع النظر إلى الأعلى؟
- Dave, stop it. - Why?
- ديف، توقف عن ذلك. - لماذا؟
Have you seen a dog looking up?
هل رأيت كلباً ينظر إلى الأعلى؟
How about you, Van?
ماذا عنك يا فان؟
Dave, don't involve me with your nonsense.
ديف، لا تورطني في هراءك.
What about my nonsense?
وماذا عن هراءي؟
Do you want to get punched?
هل تريد أن تتلقى لكمة؟
All classes are suspended.
تم تعليق جميع الحصص الدراسية.
I repeat all classes are suspended.
أكرر، تم تعليق جميع الحصص الدراسية.
A general meeting will be held at the conference room.
سيعقد اجتماع عام في قاعة المؤتمرات.
1:30 P.M. Mandatory.
الساعة 1:30 مساءً إلزامية.
I don't like this.
لا يعجبني هذا.
I have a bad feeling.
لدي شعور سيء.
Whatever their plans is
مهما كانت خططهم
we stay together.
سنبقى معاً.
I swear I have no idea.
أقسم أنني لا أعرف.
Do you know anything about this?
هل لديك أي معلومات عن هذا؟
Promise
يعد
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
- What's happening here? - How long will this take?
- ما الذي يحدث هنا؟ - كم سيستغرق هذا من الوقت؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي أي فكرة.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
مساء الخير سيداتي وسادتي.
Are you tired of this hellhole?
هل سئمت من هذا المكان البائس؟
Good news.
أخبار سارة.
Soon freedom will be within your grasp.
قريبًا ستكون الحرية في متناول يديك.
Matt?
مات؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Something's wrong here.
هناك خطأ ما هنا.
Nazzer and Nicky aren't here.
نازر ونيكي ليسا هنا.
Any day now
في أي يوم من الأيام
your suffering will end.
ستنتهي معاناتك.
From Philippine High University
من جامعة الفلبين العليا
to Hell University.
إلى جامعة الجحيم.
This place has been a witness of your resiliency and strength.
لقد كان هذا المكان شاهداً على صمودكم وقوتكم.
But all things come to an end.
لكن لكل شيء نهاية.
Even if this story reaches its end
حتى لو وصلت هذه القصة إلى نهايتها
it won't be forgotten.
لن يُنسى ذلك.
You will all remain within this place's story.
ستبقون جميعاً جزءاً من تاريخ هذا المكان.
We have been experimenting on a formula for years now.
لقد كنا نجري تجارب على تركيبة معينة لسنوات حتى الآن.
A formula that can bring back the dead.
تركيبة قادرة على إعادة الموتى إلى الحياة.
What is this nonsense again?
ما هذا الهراء مجدداً؟
Are they joking?
هل يمزحون؟
Now that we've almost completed it,
والآن وقد أوشكنا على الانتهاء منه،
I'm asking everyone to cooperate one last time.
أطلب من الجميع التعاون للمرة الأخيرة.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
What's happening?
ما الذي يحدث؟
Now
الآن
all of you must rest.
يجب عليكم جميعاً أن تستريحوا.
Supremo?
الزعيم الأعلى؟
Darling
محبوب
please come back.
أرجو العودة.
I will.
أنا سوف.
Zein?
أيها؟
You're awake
أنت مستيقظ
Mia
لي
where are the others?
أين الآخرون؟
Is it just us here?
هل نحن الوحيدون هنا؟
I don't know, Zein.
لا أعرف يا زين.
I'm scared.
أنا خائف.
Zein?
أيها؟
That one.
هذا.
- Come here! - What will you do with her?
- تعال إلى هنا! - ماذا ستفعل بها؟
Stop!
قف!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Help me!
ساعدني!
Help!
يساعد!
This is all my fault, Zein.
كل هذا خطأي يا زين.
Mia
لي
what are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
This isn't your fault.
هذا ليس خطأك.
Even if you are
حتى لو كنت
all of us are at fault too.
كلنا مخطئون أيضاً.
I made a huge mistake, Zein.
لقد ارتكبت خطأً فادحاً يا زين.
Mia
لي
whatever that mistake is
أياً كان ذلك الخطأ
I don't care about it.
لا أهتم بذلك.
What's important is
المهم هو
we all escape from here.
سنهرب جميعاً من هنا.
Thank you, Zein.
شكراً لك يا زين.
Your forgiveness is important to me
مسامحتك مهمة بالنسبة لي
because I don’t think I can forgive myself.
لأنني لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أسامح نفسي.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
You need to be strong.
عليك أن تكون قوياً.
I lied.
لقد كذبت.
I didn't find the map that led us here by chance.
لم أجد الخريطة التي قادتنا إلى هنا بالصدفة.
Guys!
شباب!
I think we're almost there.
أعتقد أننا على وشك الوصول.
Are you sure this is the right path?
هل أنت متأكد من أن هذا هو المسار الصحيح؟
Wow.
رائع.
I never pegged you as a complainer, Zein.
لم أعتبرك أبدًا شخصًا كثير الشكوى يا زين.
You've always liked these kinds of things.
لطالما أحببت هذه الأشياء.
Because when I make the plans,
لأنني عندما أضع الخطط،
I use GPS not a rusty old map!
أستخدم نظام تحديد المواقع العالمي (GPS) وليس خريطة قديمة صدئة!
True.
حقيقي.
This map is legit!
هذه الخريطة حقيقية!
If that's legit, where did you find it?
إذا كان هذا صحيحاً، فأين وجدته؟
Just trust me.
ثق بي فقط.
Remember how I used to sleep over at your house?
أتذكر كيف كنت أنام في منزلك؟
I kept noticing Ate Alison.
ظللت ألاحظ وجود أليسون.
She kept leaving the house at night
كانت تغادر المنزل ليلاً باستمرار
carrying this huge bag.
حمل هذه الحقيبة الضخمة.
I tried to find out what’s inside that bag.
حاولت أن أعرف ما بداخل تلك الحقيبة.
And they were documents
وكانت عبارة عن وثائق
operations briefs
موجزات العمليات
unusual phones and.
هواتف غير عادية و.
I saw a gun.
رأيت مسدساً.
I thought you were just scaring us when you said.
ظننت أنك كنت تخيفنا فقط عندما قلت ذلك.
Ate Allison is a secret agent.
آتي أليسون عميلة سرية.
It turns out you were telling the truth.
اتضح أنك كنت تقول الحقيقة.
I heard her one night
سمعتها ذات ليلة
talking to someone over the phone,
التحدث مع شخص ما عبر الهاتف،
holding the map that brought us here.
حاملين الخريطة التي أوصلتنا إلى هنا.
This place is one of her missions.
هذا المكان هو إحدى مهماتها.
Mia...
لي...
I got curious, Zein.
انتابني الفضول يا زين.
I don't know what got into me
لا أعرف ما الذي أصابني
when I stole the map
عندما سرقت الخريطة
from her room.
من غرفتها.
I couldn't even understand her notes.
لم أستطع حتى فهم ملاحظاتها.
What I know is
ما أعرفه هو
she was trying to find.
كانت تحاول أن تجد.
Hell University.
جامعة الجحيم.
I'm sorry, Zein.
أنا آسف يا زين.
A lot things happened to us because Mia brought us here.
لقد حدثت لنا أشياء كثيرة لأن ميا أحضرتنا إلى هنا.
Our lives have been in constant danger.
لقد كانت حياتنا في خطر دائم.
Lift it up!
ارفعها!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Okay, there.
حسناً، ها هو ذا.
Hurry.
عجل.
We can use this. Hurry!
يمكننا استخدام هذا. أسرع!
Get out of the way. Hurry!
ابتعد عن الطريق. أسرع!
Hurry up.
أسرع.
The sofa!
الأريكة!
Faster, Dave!
أسرع يا ديف!
What's happening here?
ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
Dave, hurry!
ديف، أسرع!
Use that, Dave! Hurry up will you?
استخدم هذا يا ديف! أسرع قليلاً!
They're here.
إنهم هنا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Who's the red masked guy?
من هو الرجل ذو القناع الأحمر؟
Matt's unconscious!
مات فاقد للوعي!
What happened to Matt?
ماذا حدث لمات؟
Matt!
مات!
Bro!
أخ!
Wake him up!
أيقظه!
Bro, wake up!
يا أخي، استيقظ!
Zein, what happened to the two of you?
زين، ماذا حدث لكما؟
Where's Zein?
أين زين؟
They drank the same thing.
كانوا يشربون نفس الشيء.
What is happening to her?
ما الذي يحدث لها؟
Nurse, please do something!
يا ممرضة، أرجوكِ افعلي شيئاً!
Whoever is responsible for this.
أياً كان المسؤول عن هذا.
I swear I will never forgive them.
أقسم أنني لن أسامحهم أبداً.
Mia!
لي!
Your name was in my locker!
كان اسمك موجوداً في خزانتي!
- Mia! - Mia, enough!
- ميا! - ميا، كفى!
Stop it, Mia!
توقفي عن ذلك يا ميا!
Enough, Mia.
كفى يا ميا.
I need to kill you!
أريد قتلك!
Mia!
لي!
I don't know what to feel about this.
لا أعرف ما هو شعوري حيال هذا الأمر.
How many times have we faced death in this place?
كم مرة واجهنا الموت في هذا المكان؟
Mia?
لي؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
Is she still alive?
هل ما زالت على قيد الحياة؟
You defended yourself.
لقد دافعت عن نفسك.
You didn't do anything wrong.
لم تفعل أي شيء خاطئ.
Let's go, Jerome!
هيا بنا يا جيروم!
What about her?
وماذا عنها؟
There's so much blood, Jerome!
هناك الكثير من الدماء يا جيروم!
We have to go!
علينا أن نذهب!
Please.
لو سمحت.
Dave.
ديف.
But still...
لكن مع ذلك...
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
What's important to me is that my friends are still alive.
الأهم بالنسبة لي هو أن أصدقائي ما زالوا على قيد الحياة.
The wound is deep!
الجرح عميق!
It's my fault we're here.
أنا السبب في وجودنا هنا.
I hope you told us about this from the start.
أتمنى أن تكون قد أخبرتنا بهذا الأمر منذ البداية.
We can't do anything about it anymore.
لم يعد بإمكاننا فعل أي شيء حيال ذلك.
This is our reality now.
هذا هو واقعنا الآن.
This won't end like this.
لن ينتهي الأمر على هذا النحو.
This is just the beginning.
هذه مجرد البداية.
Take her.
خذها.
No!
لا!
No, don't take her!
لا، لا تأخذها!
Stop!
قف!
Let her go!
اسمح لها أن تذهب!
Zein!
ماذا!
Take her too.
خذها معك أيضاً.
Mia!
لي!
Zein!
ماذا!
Stop!
قف!
Run, Mia!
اركضي يا ميا!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
I said let me go!
قلت دعوني أذهب!
- Hurry up! - I'm on it!
- أسرع! - أنا في الطريق!
Hurry!
عجل!
Mia!
لي!
- Mia, over here! - Dave!
- ميا، تعالي إلى هنا! - ديف!
Mia!
لي!
- Mia! - Faster!
- ميا! - أسرع!
Please, hurry!
أرجوك، أسرع!
Mia, I'm glad you're safe.
ميا، أنا سعيد لأنكِ بخير.
Where are the others?
أين الآخرون؟
- Where's Zein and Matt? - Where are they?
- أين زين ومات؟ - أين هما؟
Zein will follow us out.
سيتبعنا زين إلى الخارج.
Matt's not with us.
مات ليس معنا.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Shit, let's go!
يا إلهي، هيا بنا!
Let's go! Hurry!
هيا بنا! أسرعوا!
Hurry! Faster!
أسرع! أسرع!
Run!
يجري!
Everyone hurry!
أسرعوا جميعاً!
Watch your feet!
انتبه لقدميك!
Follow Jerome!
اتبع جيروم!
Faster! Hurry!
أسرع! أسرع!
Guys, over here!
يا شباب، تعالوا إلى هنا!
That's the last batch.
هذه هي الدفعة الأخيرة.
Dave!
ديف!
Let's go, Mia!
هيا بنا يا ميا!
We will be together soon.
سنكون معاً قريباً.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Where's Zein?
أين زين؟
Where are they?
أين هم؟
You two...
أنتما الاثنان...
What did you do?
ماذا فعلت؟
Where were you earlier?
أين كنتَ سابقاً؟
Hey
يا
calm down.
اهدأ.
We saved you when they were dragging you out of the conference room.
لقد أنقذناك عندما كانوا يسحبونك خارج قاعة المؤتمرات.
I heard them, Luke and Madam Violet, on the comms.
سمعتهم، لوك والسيدة فيوليت، عبر جهاز الاتصال.
They warned him about the gas attack.
لقد حذروه من الهجوم بالغاز.
But it's too late.
لكن الوقت قد فات.
We weren't able to relay it to all the members.
لم نتمكن من إيصال ذلك إلى جميع الأعضاء.
Luke...
لوك...
I saw him earlier.
رأيته في وقت سابق.
We've known for a while that there's a traitor among the Black Blood Gang.
لقد كنا نعلم منذ فترة أن هناك خائناً بين عصابة الدم الأسود.
Someone leaking info to the admin.
شخص ما يقوم بتسريب معلومات إلى المسؤول.
That's why we were blinded by the gas attack
لهذا السبب أعمى الهجوم بالغاز أعيننا
because our eyes on the operation
لأن أعيننا على العملية
is the traitor.
هو الخائن.
We need to find him.
علينا أن نجده.
He's the one who knows where they kept the students.
هو الشخص الوحيد الذي يعرف أين احتجزوا الطلاب.
And your friends.
وأصدقاؤك.
Zein was taken too.
تم القبض على زين أيضاً.
I need to find her.
أحتاج أن أجدها.
Wow
رائع
you really love her, don't you?
أنت تحبها حقاً، أليس كذلك؟
I loved her
أحببتها
ever since.
ومنذ ذلك الحين.
And you'll sacrifice your life for her?
وهل ستضحي بحياتك من أجلها؟
Yes
نعم
cause she will do the same for me and her friends.
لأنها ستفعل الشيء نفسه من أجلي ومن أجل صديقاتها.
She values her friends' lives
إنها تُقدّر حياة أصدقائها
more than her own life.
أكثر من حياتها.
She may be hot headed
قد تكون سريعة الغضب
and quick to fight
وسريع في القتال
but
لكن
that’s Zein.
هذا زين.
No matter how many of Violet's men I need to fight
مهما كان عدد رجال فيوليت الذين أحتاج إلى قتالهم
no one can stop me.
لا أحد يستطيع إيقافي.
I wasn't wrong in choosing you.
لم أكن مخطئاً في اختيارك.
But don't act on your own.
لكن لا تتصرف بمفردك.
Especially while we don't know where they kept the others yet.
خاصة وأننا لا نعرف أين احتفظوا بالآخرين بعد.
We need to regroup.
نحتاج إلى إعادة تنظيم صفوفنا.
We should take care of Luke first.
ينبغي أن نعتني بلوك أولاً.
Fine.
بخير.
Okay?
تمام؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hello, secretary.
مرحباً يا سكرتيرة.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
I'm better than fine.
أنا بخير وأكثر من ذلك.
Well this is our hidden laboratory.
حسنًا، هذا هو مختبرنا السري.
Supremo will come for me.
سيأتي الزعيم الأعلى إليّ.
You don't know him like I do.
أنت لا تعرفه كما أعرفه.
He's coming.
إنه قادم.
Haven't you all felt angry?
ألم تشعروا جميعاً بالغضب؟
Angry from their injustice?
غاضبون من الظلم الذي تعرضوا له؟
Nobody move!
لا أحد يتحرك!
Guys, get down.
يا شباب، انزلوا.
What are the chances?
ما هي الاحتمالات؟
Aside from the special treatment that Supremo has been giving you
بصرف النظر عن المعاملة الخاصة التي يقدمها لك سوبريمو
there's actually something special about you.
هناك شيء مميز فيك بالفعل.
An exceptionally rare blood type
فصيلة دم نادرة للغاية
with an exceptionally rare blood component.
مع وجود مكون دموي نادر للغاية.
They're preparing her for the extraction.
إنهم يجهزونها لعملية الاستخراج.
Violet's going to get what she wants.
ستحصل فيوليت على ما تريد.
This hell will finally end.
سينتهي هذا الجحيم أخيراً.
I am Supremo.
أنا الزعيم الأعلى.
I will not fail.
لن أفشل.
Seal the door!
أغلق الباب!
Ou don't know him like I do.
أنت لا تعرفه كما أعرفه.
He's coming for me.
إنه قادم إليّ.